techbeamers.com 2017-11-21

# TechBeamers - Privacy Policy for Users and Readers

## Privacy policy for www.techbeamers.com

### Introduction.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to serve the users of this site for safety and better user-experience. It’ll guide those who may have concerns regarding their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that one can use to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

 **1.  **To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings that you may like.

 **2.  **To improve our website in order to better serve you.

 **3.  **To allow us in delivering better services. For example, responding to customer service requests.

 **4.  **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

 **5.  **To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

### How do we protect visitor information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use cookies to:

 **1.  **Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

 **2.  **Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf. You can choose to have your computer warn for cookies, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You can configure this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way for modifying the cookies.

If you disable cookies, then some features won’t be available. But it won’t affect the user’s experience that makes your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still use the site.

### Third Party Disclosure.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third Party Links.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Online Privacy Policy Only.

This online privacy policy applies only to information that we collect through our website. It doesn’t involve any offline data.

### Your Consent.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can. Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Changes to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Document updated on 23rd Oct’ 2016.

### Contact us.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, then you may contact us using the information below.

 **http://www.techbeamers.com**  
**admin@techbeamers.com**
